Guide to the New York State Council on the Arts Electronic Media and Film Program records, [ca. 1960-2011]
New York State Council on the Arts Electronic Media and Film Program records
- Individuals A-Z
  - J-M
    - Kopple, Barbara - Cabin Creek Workshop Environmental Center, c. 1985 (Box 12, Folder 130)
      Grant application 1985-1986 for Plant Closing in the American Workplace: The Cutting Edge
    - Kotin, Lisa - Funambules (PE 153), 1990-1991 (Box 12, Folder 131)
      Grant application 1990-1991 for Temporary Girl
    - Kowalski, Libby - Council for the Arts for Cortland (Ic 79), c. 1985 (Box 12, Folder 132)
      Grant application 1985-1986 for Black and White; letter of agreement; final report form
    - Kramer, Margia, undated (Box 12, Folder 133)
      Grant application for New Wozzeck
    - Kreiger, Arthur - New York New Music Ensemble (CH 43) (IND), undated (Box 12, Folder 134)
      CV and biography for Arthur Kreiger
    - Krider, Annoel (CR 73), c. 1989 (Box 12, Folder 135)
      Grant application FY89 for four textile art pieces
    - Krishanan, Indu - Women Make Movies (VD 131) (IND), c. 1988, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 136)
      Grant application 1988-1989 for Home Truths; progress report, letter of agreement (undated, 1992)
    - Kroehling, Richard, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 137)
      Grant application FY99 for World's End; letter of agreement
    - Kubota, Shigeko - Video Art Experimental Television Center (VA 23), undated (Box 12, Folder 138)
      Grant application (project description has faded)
    - Kupferman, Meyer - Woodstock Chamber (C 156), undated (Box 12, Folder 139)
      Sample of work submitted form; biography for Meyer Kupferman
    - Kuivila, Ron - NYFA (AI 112), c. 1989 (Box 12, Folder 140)
      Grant application 1989-1990 for Dolci Mura
    - Kuras, Ellen - Women Make Movies (VD 128) (IND), c. 1994 (Box 12, Folder 141)
      Grant application FY94 for Letter to my Father
    - Kushner, Tony - Red Wing Preforming Group, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 142)
      Project description for A Bright Room Called Day; correspondence
    - Kurihara, Nanako - Women Makes Movies (VD 133) (IND), c. 1992 (Box 12, Folder 143)
      Grant application 1992-1993 for From Woman to Woman
    - Kyi, Daresha - Women Make Movies (VD 169) (IND), c. 1989, 1990, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 144)
      Grant application (1989-1990, 1990, FY95) for Counting the Ways: The Love Series and Visions from the Void/
    - Laderman, Ezra (OR 128), c. 1985 (Box 12, Folder 145)
      Grant application (undated); letter of agreement (1985) for violin Concerto
    - Lafond, Jody - Squeaky Wheel, c. 1987 (Box 12, Folder 146)
      Grant application 1987-1988 for Going Places; letter of agreement
    - Lake, Oliver (S 128), undated (Box 12, Folder 147)
      Grant application (undated) for music composition
    - Lam, Bun-Ching - Bang on a Can (ST 93), c. 1992 (Box 12, Folder 148)
      Grant application FY92 for music composition
    - Lang, David - Dance Continuum (SC 46), c. 1992 (Box 12, Folder 149)
    - Lasch, Pat - Franklin Furnace Archive Inc., c. 1984 (Box 12, Folder 150)
      Grant application 1984-1985 for If you Make a Mistake, Put a Rose on it
    - Lattanzi, Barbara - Hallwalls (VA 115), c. 1989-1990 (Box 12, Folder 151)
      Grant application 1989-1990 for Fishy Aura; internal memo with hand-written comments
    - Le Baron, Anne and Terese Svoboda = Harvestworks (SF 69), c. 1990 (Box 12, Folder 152)
      Grant application FY90 for Orphans; letter of agreement
    - Leach, Mary Jane - Experimental Intermedia Foundation (SD 45) (IND), c. 1991-1992 (Box 12, Folder 153)
      Grant application FY92 for Pipe Dreams; letter of agreement
    - LeCompte, Elizabeth - Wooster Group (VN 117), c. 1990-1997 (Box 12, Folder 154)
      Grant application (FY92, undated, FY97) for Kisser, White Homeland Commando and Wrong Guys; letter of agreement (1990, 1991)
    - Lee, Leslie - Frederick Douglas Creative Arts Center, undated (Box 12, Folder 155)
      Letter of intent, Director's Statement for the Frederick Douglas Creative Arts Center
    - Lee, Spike - Black Filmmaker Foundation (V 106N), c. 1984-1985 (Box 12, Folder 156)
      Grant application 1984-1985 for The Messenger; project description for She's Gotta Have It
    - Lehiardi-Laura, Roland, 1989-1992 (Box 12, Folder 157)
      Grant application (1989-1990, FY92) for documentary of poetry in Nicaragua and Teacher; letter of agreement (1987, 1991)
    - Lehrer, Warren (GR82), 1989 (Box 12, Folder 158)
      Grant application FY89 for The Portrait Series; letter of agreement
    - Leighton, Lorri - Women Makes Movies (VD 118), c. 1998 (Box 12, Folder 159)
      Grant application FY98 for Out of the Broom Closet
    - Leon, Tania - Performers Committee (CH 63), undated (Box 12, Folder 160)
      Sample of work submitted forms, CV for Tania Leon
    - Lerer, Jeffrey - Experimental Television Center (VA 175), 1995 (Box 12, Folder 161)
      Grant application (FY95) for Memory Box; letter of agreement
    - Lerner, Marilyn - Hallwalls (PA 96), c. 1989 (Box 12, Folder 162)
      Grant application c. 1989 for experimental painting installation
    - Leshin, Liz - Women Make Movies (VD 200), c. 1991 (Box 12, Folder 163)
      Grant application FY92 for Between Sky and Earth; letter of agreement
    - Levi, Robert - NYFA (VD 121), c. 1997-1998 (Box 12, Folder 164)
      Grant application (FY97, FY98) for Something to Live For: The Billy Strayhorn Story and Gordon Parks: American Photographer
    - Leung, Simon - Segue Foundation (MM 164), c. 1990-1991 (Box 12, Folder 165)
      Grant application 1990-1991 for Scar of Attachment; letter of agreement
    - Lew, Herman - Camera News (VN 121), c. 1991-1994 (Box 12, Folder 166)
      Grant application (FY92, FY94) for Moot to Mulberry and Paper Sons; letter of agreement
    - Lewis, George - Roulette Intermedium (EL 111), undated (Box 12, Folder 167)
      Sample of work submitted form; CV for George Lewis
    - Lichtenstein, Bill, c. 1997 (Box 12, Folder 168)
      Interim Report If I Get Out Alive; letter of agreement
    - Lieberson, Peter - Concert Artists Guild (CV 197), c. 1988 (Box 12, Folder 169)
      Grant application (undated) for music composition; correspondence
    - Life, Reggie - Alternative Media Information Center (VN 130), c. 1986-1988 (Box 12, Folder 170)
      Grant application (1986-1987, 1987-1988) for Reunion
    - Lin, Lana - Millenium (VE 128), c. 1995 (Box 12, Folder 171)
      Grant application FY96 for Almost Cocktail Hour; letter of agreement
    - Linhart, Henry - Experimental Intermedia Foundation (VD 141), c. 1991 (Box 12, Folder 172)
      Grant application for The Blissville Opera
    - Lindsay, Arto and Peter Scherer- Stephen Petronio Dance Company (SD 74), 1989-1990 (Box 12, Folder 173)
      Sample of work submitted form; Arto Lindsay and Peter Scherer biography; letter of agreement for music composition
    - Linney, Romulus - Theater for the New City Foundation (PW 29), 1996 (Box 12, Folder 174)
      Grant application 1996-1997 for Love Like Fire; letter of agreement
    - Linton, David (SC 138), c. 1988 (Box 12, Folder 175)
      Sample of work submitted (undated); letter of agreement for music composition (1988)
    - Lister, Ardele, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 176)
      Grant application 1985-1986 for Between Heaven and Hell: Love in my Mind; letter of agreement
    - Livingston, Jennie - Morning Star Film Association (VD 133), 1986 (Box 12, Folder 177)
      Grant application 1986-1987 for Paris is Burning; letter of agreement
    - Llorens, Raul - Media Network (VD 139) (IND), c. 1992 (Box 12, Folder 178)
      Grant application 1992-1993 for Wide Time: Surviving AIDS
    - Logan, Fern - National Urban League, Inc. (4D12), 1984 (Box 12, Folder 179)
      Grant application 1984-1985 for Photographic Portrait Project; letter of agreement; correspondence
    - Logue, Joan - NYFA (VI 122), 1988-1989 (Box 12, Folder 180)
      Grant application 1989-1990 for series of video portraits
    - Loktev, Julia - Women Make Movies, Inc. (VD 125), c. 1998 (Box 12, Folder 181)
      Grant application FY98 for Moment of Impact
    - Long, Quincy - Soho Repertory Theater, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 182)
      Grant application 1990-1991 for Yokohama Duty; letter of agreement
    - Long, Zhou - Brooklyn Philharmonic (CH 49) (IND), 1993, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 183)
      Grant application FY96 for music composition; letter of agreement (1993)
    - Longo, Robert - Burchfield Art Center (P 101), 1986-1987 (Box 12, Folder 184)
      Grant application 1986-1987 for Killing Angels; letter of agreement
    - Lopez, Tom (RA 152), 1986-1988 (Box 12, Folder 185)
      Grant application (1986-1987, 1988-1989) for Dreams of Rio and Saratoga Springs; final report; letter of agreement (1986, 1988)
    - Lovejoy, Margot - East End Arts Council (IM 103), c. 1986 (Box 12, Folder 186)
      Grant application 1986-1987 for Cloud Stage V
    - Lovell, Lexy and Michael Uys - Media Network (VD 132), 1995 (Box 12, Folder 187)
      Grant application FY96 for Riding the Rails: Children of the Great Depression; letter of agreement
    - Lowinger, Leslie (GR 89), 1989 (Box 12, Folder 188)
    - Lucas, Marty - Media Network (SP 143), c. 1992 (Box 12, Folder 189)
      Grant application 1992-1993 for Paper Tiger Television
    - Lucier, Mary - Parabola (VI 187) (IND), 1986-1995 (Box 12, Folder 190)
      Grant application (1986-1987, 1988-1989, FY95) for Avatrix-X, Noah's Raven and Last Rites (Positano)
    - Lum, Mary - Pyramid Arts Center (GR 99), c. 1990 (Box 12, Folder 191)
      Grant application c. 1990 for The Final Results of Psychoanalytic Treatment
    - Luo, Jing Jing - Moving Earth (SD 77), c. 1990 (Box 12, Folder 192)
    - Lurie, John - Wooster Group, Inc (SL 54), undated (Box 12, Folder 193)
      CV for John Lurie
    - Lynch, Kara - Camera News, Inc (VD 143), c. 1997 (Box 12, Folder 194)
      Grant application FY97 for Africa in Russia: The Diaspora
    - Lyons, Danny - Hallwalls (FD 110), c. 1985 (Box 12, Folder 195)
      Grant application 1985-1986 for Memories of the Southern Civil Rights Movement
    - Lyons - Video Art Media Study (VA 38), c. 1984 (Box 12, Folder 196)
      Grant application (undated) for Oo-Bop-Sha-Bam
    - Ma, Amanda - Panarts (VN 157), c. 1987, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 197)
      Grant application (1987-1988, FY91) for Choices and Living Rooms; letter of agreement (1987)
    - Ma, Nichole - Film News Now (VN 149)(, c. 1989 (Box 12, Folder 198)
      Grant application 1989-1990 for Choices; CV for Michelle Mahrer
    - Mackey, Steven (CH 143), c. 1987 (Box 12, Folder 199)
      sameple of work submitted form; letter of agreement (1987) for music composition
    - Madansky, Cynthia - Women Make Movies, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 200)
    - Magill, Mark - Radio Catskill (RA 149), c. 1985, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 201)
      Grant application (1985-1986, 1992-1993) for Casting Fair Ophelia and Dictionary
    - Maguire, Matthew - Creation Production Company (PW 30), c. 1996 (Box 12, Folder 202)
      Grant application 1996-1997 for Chaos
    - Maldonado, Victoria (VN 164), 1988 (Box 12, Folder 203)
      Grant application 1988-1989 for Cafe Norte y Sur; letter of agreement
    - Malina, Amy - Film and Video Workshop (SF 141), undated (Box 12, Folder 204)
      CV for Amy Malina
    - Malinowitz, Harriet, c. 1990 (Box 12, Folder 205)
      Grant application 1990-1991 for Points of Departure
    - Malpede, John, c. 1984 (Box 12, Folder 206)
      panel comments FY84 for conceptual television spots
    - Mangolte, Babette - Parabola Arts Foundation (FN 137), c. 1987 (Box 12, Folder 207)
      Grant application (undated) for The Space We Deserve
    - Maple, Jessie (VN 166), 1985-1988 (Box 12, Folder 208)
      Grant application (1985-1986, 1986-1987, 1988-1989) for Twice as Nice; correspondence
    - Mar, Stephani and Shirin Neshat (MD 92), c. 1985, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 209)
      Grant application (1985-1986, FY89) for Urban Bubble Garden and maze project
    - Marcus, Bunita (CH 142), unadted (Box 12, Folder 210)
      Sample of work submitted forms; CV for Bunita Marcus
    - Marks, Graham - Pyramid Arts Center (4F7), c. 1984-1986 (Box 12, Folder 211)
      Grant application 1984-1985 for sandblasted ceramic sculpture; Everson Museum of Art Bulletin
    - Marks, Victoria - Dance Theater Workshop, Inc. (VA 147), c. 1996-1997 (Box 12, Folder 212)
      Grant application FY97 for dance and video project; correspondence; fliers
    - Maroney, Denman - Roulette (JZ 49) (IND), undated (Box 12, Folder 213)
      Sample of work submitted forms; CV for Denman Maroney
    - Martn, Manuel Jr. - Spanish Theater Repertory Company, c. 1990 (Box 12, Folder 214)
      Grant application 1990-1991 for Botanica
    - Martin, Steve - Parabola Arts Foundation (VD 133), 1991 (Box 12, Folder 215)
      Grant application FY92 for Good Vibrations; panel comments
    - Martino, Donald (CH 149), undated (Box 12, Folder 216)
      Sample of work submitted form; biography of Donald Martino
    - Martinovic, Igor - Samaya Foundation (VD 198) (IND), c. 1995 (Box 12, Folder 217)
      Grant application FY95 for Evil and Upside Down
    - Matheson, Katherine - The Moving Image (VD 118), c. 1985 (Box 12, Folder 218)
      Grant application 1985-1986 for Kamera Sutra
    - Matias, Bienvenida (VD 283), c. 1990 (Box 12, Folder 219)
      Grant application 1990 for Puerto Rico: America's Last Colony
    - McCallum, Bradley, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 220)
      Correspondence; press release
    - McCauley, Robbie - The Working Theater, c. 1992 (Box 12, Folder 221)
      Grant application 1992-1993 for Rhetorical Oratorio
    - McCarney, Scott - Visual Studies Workshop (Ag 107), c. 1986 (Box 12, Folder 222)
      Grant application 1986-1987 for Memory Loss
    - McClintock, Ernie, undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
      director's statement for theater project
    - McCray, Melvin (VD 157), c. 1988 (Box 13, Folder 2)
      Grant application 198-1989 for Dollie Robinson: The Woman and Her Times
    - McGough - Hallwalls (SP 219), c. 1992 (Box 13, Folder 3)
      Grant application 1992-1993 for Open City
    - McFerran, Mary and Diane Torr - Colab (CL 162), c. 1986 (Box 13, Folder 4)
      Grant application (1986-1987) for Mata Hari video project
    - McIntyre, Earl (JZ 191), undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
      Sample of work submitted form; biography for Earl McIntyre
    - McLaughlin, Sheila - Collective for Living Cinema (VN 156), c.1985-1989 (Box 13, Folder 6)
      Grant application (1985-1986, 1986-1987, 1989-1990) for Committed; adaptation of The Spanish Military Nun; Fat Girls from Hell
    - McMillan, Ann - Quintet of the Americas (CH 129), undated (Box 13, Folder 7)
      Sample of work submitted; CV for Ann McMillan
    - Meckley, Diana - Harvestworks (E 184), 1989-1990 (Box 13, Folder 8)
      Grant application FY90 for The Evolving Artifact; letter of agreement
    - Medley, Cassandra, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 9)
      CV for Cassandra Medley and commission report
    - Mednick, Jonathan, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 10)
      publicity information for Dita and the Family Business
    - Meieran, David (VD 160), 1988-1992 (Box 13, Folder 11)
      Grant application (1988-1989, 1991-1992, 1992-1993) for Testing the Limits: NYC (Part 1 and Part 2 and Under Attack; press clippings' press releases; fliers
    - Mekas, Jonas - Film Art Fund (VD 166), c.1987 (Box 13, Folder 12)
      Grant application 1987-1988 for This is My Life on Earth
    - Mendieta, Ana, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Mertes, Cara - Women Make Movies (VA 125)(IND), c.1991 (Box 13, Folder 14)
      Grant application 1991-1992 for Under Siege
    - Mertin, Roger - Light Work Visual Studies (4D 5), c. 1989 (Box 13, Folder 15)
      Grant application 1984-1985 for Seasonal Festivals and Historical Pageants project
    - Meyer, Marlene, c. 1989 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Michaelson, Alan - Public Art Fund (SC 106), c. 1990 (Box 13, Folder 17)
      Grant application c. 1990 for Warpoes
    - Miles, Ginger - Harvestworks (RA 156), c. 1986, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 18)
      Grant application (1986-1987,1992-1993) for Moisha and Cherokee Nation: Untold Treasures
    - Miles, William - Miles Educational Film Lab (VD 138), 1992 (Box 13, Folder 19)
      Grant application FY92 for Liberators: Fighting on Two Fronts in World War II; news clippings
    - Millar, Cam - Ice Theater of New York (SL 56), c. 1997-1998 (Box 13, Folder 20)
      final report form (1997-1998) for music composition; CV for Cam Millar, program; flier
    - Miller, Peter - Media Network (VD 201), 1995 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Millner, Sherry - Women Make Movies (VA 134), c. 1989 (Box 13, Folder 22)
      Grant application 1989-1990 for Wet Palms
    - Minahan, Daniel - NYFA VN 136) (IND), 1993, undated (Box 13, Folder 23)
      Grant application (FY94 and undated) for The Celestial Child; letter of agreement
    - Mitchell, Edith (CR 45), c. 1987 (Box 13, Folder 24)
      Grant application 1987-1988 for year of sponsored work in quilting
    - Miyagawa, Chiori - Dance Theater Workshop, Inc. (CO 33), c. 1996 (Box 13, Folder 25)
      Grant application 1996-1997 for Out of the Shadows II
    - Mohr, Nicholasa - Henry Street Settlement (WS029)(IND), c. 1998 (Box 13, Folder 26)
      Grant application 1998-1999 for Nilda
    - Monk, Meredith - House Foundation for the Arts (DI 35), 1987, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 27)
      Grant application 1986-1987 for Book of Days; letter of agreement (1987, 1995)
    - Montano, Linda - The New Museum (P 117), c. 1986 (Box 13, Folder 28)
      Grant application 1986-1987 for Seven Years of Living At - Linda Montano
    - Montoya, Ivonne Patricia - Women Make Movies (VN 206)(IND), c. 1995 (Box 13, Folder 29)
      Grant application FY95 for El Culebrero, La Muerte de Un Colombiano y un Acordionista Dominicano Que No Esta; translation
    - Moore, Alan - Video Art Collaborative Projects (VA 4), c. 1984 (Box 13, Folder 30)
      Grant application 1984-1985 for Studio Melee; CV for Alan Moore; press clippings; copies of sketches and plans
    - Moore, Andrew, 1982-1983 (Box 13, Folder 31)
      Grant application (undated) for untitled photography project, correspondence; letter of agreement; quarterly report; 35mm slides
    - Moore, Carmen - Skymusic (SD 54), 1987, 1991, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 32)
      Grant application FY92 for musical composition; correspondence; fliers; news clippings
    - Moore, Frank and Jim Self - Primary Performance Group (PE 154), c.1986-1991 (Box 13, Folder 33)
      Grant application (1986-1987, 1990-1991) for The Miller's Wife and painting project; letter of agreement
    - Moret, Ramon Rivera, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 34)
      Correspondence; CV for Suketu Mehta
    - grant application (1985-1986, 1989-1990) for New Roads, Louisiana and Dr. Death; correspondence; news clippings; letter of agreement, 1985, 1987, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - Morris, Lawrence Butch - Wooster Group (ST 141), undated (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - Mouris, Frank and Caroline - L.E.A.P. (FA 158), c. 1986-1987 (Box 13, Folder 37)
      Grant application 1986-1987 for Laff Trak; letter of agreement
    - Mulligan, Gerry - Seacliff (C 132), undated (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - Mullins, Carol - Talking Band, Inc (WS030) (IND), undated (Box 13, Folder 39)
      biography for Carol Mullins
    - Muntadas, Antonio - Video Art Electronics Arts Intermix (VA 14), undated (Box 13, Folder 40)
      Grant application (undated) for Between the Frames
    - Murillo, Mario - Media Network (VD 210)(IND), c. 1995 (Box 13, Folder 41)
      Grant application FY95 for Caminos Del Pueblo: The Struggle of Columbia's Indigenous Communities
    - Murray, David - UBW, Inc. (SC 61), undated, c. 1997 (Box 13, Folder 42)
      Grant application (undated) for music composition; final report form FY 1997-1998
    - Myers, Rita, c. 1985, 1991-1992 (Box 13, Folder 43)
      Grant application (1985-1986, 1991-1992, 1992-1993) for The Swan Flies Up, Correspondences: Day into Night into Day and Crucible
  - N-R
    - Negrin, Lee - Foundry Theater (PW 36), c. 1996 (Box 13, Folder 44)
      Grant application 1996-1997 for The Valley of Lao
    - Nair, Mira - Asian Cine-Vision (F 120 D), c. 1984 (Box 13, Folder 45)
      Grant application 1984-1985 for unnamed film project
    - Nance, Marilyn - Akuaba (EF 120), 1986 (Box 13, Folder 46)
      Grant application 1986-1987 for Religion; letter of agreement
    - Naphtali, Dafina, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 47)
    - Nath, Pandit Pran - MELA (V76), undated, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 48)
      Grant application (undated) for music composition; letter of agreement (1986)
    - Navazio, Michela - Musicains of Brooklyn (JZ 95), 1990, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 49)
      Grant application FY90 for music composition; letter of agreement (1990, 1995)
    - Nazario, Zydnia (VD 190), 1988 (Box 13, Folder 50)
      Grant application 1988-1989 for Linking Islands; letter of agreement
    - Negroponte, George - Real Life Magazine (PA 115), 1987-1988 (Box 13, Folder 51)
      Grant application 1987-1988 for Encaustic Painting project; letter of agreement
    - Nelson, Stanley - Center for the Study of Music (VD 190), 1990 (Box 13, Folder 52)
      Grant application 1990 for a film on the methadone program
    - Nerwin, Diane - Standby Program, Inc. (VD 169), 1996 (Box 13, Folder 53)
      Grant application FY97 for Under the Skin Game; letter of agreement
    - Newman, Betsy - Henry Street Settlement (VD 169), 1988-1989 (Box 13, Folder 54)
      Grant application 1988-1989 for The Spirit of the Dream: The Grimke Sisters of South Carolina; letter of agreement; progress report
    - Niblock, Phill, Steve Cellum, and Lona Foote - Elaine Summers E.I.F. (AA 173), c. 1986, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 55)
      Grant application (1986-1987, FY92) for music compositions
    - Nierenberg, George - Folk Traditions (VD 155), c. 1985-1986, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 56)
      Grant application (1985-1986, FY86, FY96) for untitled film about stardom focusing on child stars, Drum and Bugle and Sweet Inspiration
    - Nieves-Cruz, Yvette and Angela Moscarella - Alternative Media Information Center (VD 158), c. 1985 (Box 13, Folder 57)
      Grant application 1985-1986 for Frente a Frente: El Movimiento Anti-Imperialista Cultural y Politico en Mexico
    - Ning, Steven - Film News Now (VN 135), 1985 (Box 13, Folder 58)
      Grant application 1985-1986 for Freckled Rice; letter of agreement. Note on folder "Artist Deceased"
    - Noble, Nigel (VD 193), 1988-1990 (Box 13, Folder 59)
      Grant application (1988-1989, 1989-1990) for Sarafina!: The Documentary and A Voice to the Voiceless; letters of agreement
    - Norman, Peter, c. 2001 (Box 13, Folder 60)
      Grant application FY01 for Opera
    - Norwood, Vernon and Nancy (Video Art Media Study (VA 41), undated (Box 13, Folder 61)
      Grant application (undated) for untitled experimental narrative
    - Noschese, Christine - Media Network (VD 219) (IND), c. 1985, 1993, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 62)
      Grant application 91984-1985, FY95) for Metropolitan Avenue and Class in New York City; letter of agreement (1993)
    - Nunns, Stephen - Mabou Mines (CO 62), c. 1994 (Box 13, Folder 63)
      Grant application 1994-1995 for The Boys in the Basement
    - Oblowitz, Michael and David Goldberg - Committee for the Visual Arts (F 126E), c. 1984 (Box 13, Folder 64)
      Grant application (1984-1985) for The Arcades Project: New York
    - Ochs, Jacki - Human Arts Association (VD 147), 1991 (Box 13, Folder 65)
      Grant application (FY92) for Neighbor; letter of agreement
    - O'Geary, Lorraine, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 66)
      proposal for Art on Parade; letter of agreement
    - O'Hagan, John - NYFA (VD 160), 1995 (Box 13, Folder 67)
      Grant application FY96 for The Honeymoon Years; letter of agreement